(Howard:)Did I tell you about the night my retainer
floated out of my mouth into the airlock?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, you mentioned it once or twice.
(Howard:)So here we are.
(Howard:)Just a couple of young newlyweds.
What to do?
(Howard:)What to do to you?
(Howard:)Astronaut Wolowitz reporting for booty.
(Howard:)Preparing thrusters.
(Howard:)We have liftoff.
(Howard:)- Are we clear to jettison that nightgown?
- Okay, we need to talk.
(Sheldon:)- What?
- Howie, I know you went to space...
...and I'm incredibly proud of you.
But you might wanna try and
not bring it up every minute.
(Howard:)I don't talk about it every minute.
Tonight at dinner you went on about it
for an hour straight.